{
    "id": "a9d00b3a530e45daac4df04789e91879",
    "title": "General English Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He distributed the sweets ………………… .. the children.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "between",
                "within",
                "among"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d35c347cb20543ce96ceb3bc9b648741"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following words means the opposite of the word ‘generous’?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "foolish",
                "lavish",
                "dull",
                "economical"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "2b77422900764b078ba9be3d87fd634c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither of them ………………….. fit for the job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0a0e2b4e6a8c47d58e00e304a205fece"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘This building is very old,’ the postmaster said. ‘I have to find an ………………… . building for the post office.’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "alternative",
                "alternate",
                "alternant"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c0eddc8fa4a5444c80019e4901d369ee"
        },
        {
            "question": "When I met her, she ………………… .. as a lecturer in a college.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was working",
                "has been working",
                "is working"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1b3ab3c5d3264e5caa15239dfa3bb321"
        },
        {
            "question": "The sentence ‘Had I worked harder, I would have won’ means",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I worked harder and won",
                "I worked harder, yet I didn’t win",
                "I did not work harder, yet I won",
                "I didn’t work harder, and I didn’t win"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "45823a478a57451191706a789217d68c"
        },
        {
            "question": "If I had not opened the door, the cat ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will not jump out",
                "would not jump out",
                "would not have jumped out"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "12b7ff8014024071bb0ec0d393e2ea37"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… . the newspaper, when the doorbell ……………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am reading, rang",
                "was reading, rang",
                "had read, rang"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a9d8a375f7fe4f0ea962ffd5a346027a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The opposite of the word sympathy is ................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "empathy",
                "pity",
                "apathy"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "96e8eb1b7cc740e38d700e765df5bac7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am going to ………………… . library.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "any",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6e0fb58d21ce4c1a994dcb3ef4a31f32"
        }
    ]
}